<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title><![CDATA[BellsForStacy]]></title>
        <description><![CDATA[BellsForStacy]]></description>
        <link>https://thegrid.ai/bellsforstacy/</link>
        <generator>The Grid</generator>
        <lastBuildDate>Sun, 20 Mar 2016 19:04:17 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <atom:link href="https://thegrid.ai/bellsforstacy/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Mirrorless]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>Mirrorless</h1><p>On the day of the birthday party for sweetie face my camera broke.  Some investigating led me to the already assumed conclusion that the lovely shutter on my lovely NIKON D7000 had - after roughly 300,000 actuations - died.

This was not it's first threat to leave us.  There were other issues I had worked through.  There was the time Lewis left it on an airplane.  And that time (which was about a year ago to the day) whilst I was mentally calculating how I could afford to replace it whilst being on vacation (already a budgeting enterprise) - Lewis was talking about mirrorless cameras.  I was (probably angrily) throwing that idea off because mirrorless - BAH - everyone knows DSLR's are the best.

So thus.  Seed.  Planted.

When the camera died Lewis asked I investigate again.  Compare mirrorless and their benefits to the DSLRs and come to a conclusion.  I (probably angrily) defended my blessed DSLRs and looked up how much a straight replacement body would be and then looked up how much the newer (but still later) model would be.

In the end, I went to the store by myself.  And I picked them up and took pictures, and asked questions and, in the end, I ended up with the mirrorless.

Why? 

Well.  Because it's so much lighter and smaller.  Now obviously this depends on which lens you have on.  I have a 24-240 and it's huge so that's not a big sell feature there.  But with the 50mm lens on it's much more manageable.

I don't know.  We're feeling each other out.  It has a lot of perks that I like.  The biggest down side I'm having is just getting to know it.  The LCD screen is easier to see but it isn't true to what they look on screen / printed.  That was true of my last as well but I was so familiar I knew how to compensate.  It will take time.

I still have my beloved NIKON.  I may fix it yet.  But.  Till then.  The introductions continue.</p><img src="https://the-grid-user-content.s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/b1efd707-dcd4-42c6-bf33-1afadc3499ac.jpg"></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/bellsforstacy/julia-tulip/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">91c1b90f-0c61-4567-b289-0555d5c570c2</guid>
            <pubDate>Sun, 20 Mar 2016 19:03:58 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>